Mom, Dad, what are you doing here
Come in and sit down
We're not going in
You two come out here
Mom, Dad
Why did you come here
I won't waste any more breath
Daniel owes two million to loan sharks
You're paying for it
I said I'm not giving him a dime
Fine
Everyone, come and look at this
Lewes is driving his in-laws to their deaths
What's going on
I heard Lewes won't give his in-laws any money
The couple's about to drink poison
If you don't pay up
Your mom and I will drink this
Mom, Dad, stop this nonsense
Give me that bottle
Cynthia
If you still care about us as parents
Then convince Lewes to pay up
Mom
Everyone, judge for yourselves
My brother-in-law spent millions on factories and land
But for just two million
He's driving his in-laws to suicide
Lewes, if you don't pay up today
I'll drink this and die at your doorstep
Good Heavens
Look at what's happening
Lewes is rich but turns his back on his family
He's just watching us die
Mom, Dad, stop it
I know exactly what kind of people you are
You value your lives too much
You'd never actually drink that